Harri Best

Full Stack Developer

Contact

http://harribest.co.uk/
LinkedIn

North Devon - Open to relocation

Key Skills

Miro & Figma

HTML & CSS

JavaScript (ES6)

React

Next.js

Node.js

PostgreSQL

MongoDB

Heroku

Netlify

Vercel

Tailwind

Express

Jest

Cypress

Git

Activities and Interests

Travel

Languages

Conversational German

Yoga/Fitness

Theatre

Sketch comedy

(writing/performing)

Building and tweaking PCs IoT device technology

Profile

Currently transitioning into the tech industry after a fulfilling decade of teaching. I bring a wealth of transferrable skills which have been invaluable when working within Agile team. I enjoy the process of creating intuitive UI/UX and applying front-end and back-end skills.

Career

April 2022 – *August* 2022

School of Code • Birmingham • Remote

- 16 week intensive full-stack development bootcamp fully remote.
- Covered JavaScript, React, Node, Express, Postgres, SQL, HTML, CSS, Agile, Git, and more – weekly pair hackathons.
- Ideating/refining concepts and creating low and high-fidelity wireframes.
- Focus on best practices, pair programming, team projects.
- Redeem, the final project for School of Code, was predominantly created using Next.js and MongoDB. Redeem was designed to serve as a platform for eco-minded creators.
- Additional UX/UI Design courses from Interaction Design Foundation.
- Created a portfolio website, including code, using React.

Sept 2020 - April 2022

Primary School Teacher • St Sidwells School • Exeter

- Delivered engaging lessons to children across two key-stages
- Subject lead for art and history defining the teaching and assessment of both subjects.
- Worked with parents and professionals on safeguarding of vulnerable students and those with special educational needs
- Enjoy public speaking in front of various audiences as a result.

February 2020 - September 2021

Teacher • Private Tutoring • Exeter

Due to the pandemic, the start time of my next teaching post was delayed. In response to this I adapted by starting my own private tutoring business.

- Created an engaging website that communicated my friendly and thorough approach to teaching.
- Organised client meetings to determine their needs and tailor a package.

 Maintained a consistent quality of communication with parents to keep them informed of their child's progress.

September 2020 – April 2022

Primary School Teacher • Kings Ash Academy • Paignton

- Coordinated a team of teaching assistants across multiple classrooms to boost children's progress lost to the pandemic.
- Focused on continuous professional development and became safeguarding lead, helping drive the development of the school.

2017 - 2018

PGCE Teacher Training • DPSC • Exeter

Throughout the year's training, I taught at two schools around Exeter whilst also attending training sessions, lectures and undergoing frequent observations and professional development.

September 2014 – July 2017

Teaching Assistant • Landkey Primary School • Landkey

During my time at Landkey Primary, I completed the Assisting Learning within Schools diploma, complimenting my work and strengthening my practice.

- Maintaining a high standard of communication and effective teaching strategies to ensure that progress is made and tracked thoroughly.
- Worked between various classrooms and key-stage teams, rapidly becoming familiar with the content and delivering lessons confidently.

July 2010 – August 2012

Team Leader & Customer Service • Tesco • Braunton

After Petroc college, this role let me save enough to attend university.

- Leading, and training, a team of colleagues by fostering a positive and collaborative working environment.
- Helping customers with issues relating to purchased products in store and online.

Education

2017 - 2018

PGCE Teacher Training • DPSC • Exeter

2016 - 2017

Assisting Learning within Schools • Diploma • Plymouth University

2011 - 2014

Theatre BA (Hons) 2:1 • The University College Falmouth

2007 - 2010

Petroc College • North Devon

National Award Theatre (Distinction)

A-Levels: Film Studies; Science in Society

AS Level: Psychology